<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Call Flows on HEUSSER.PRO</title>
        <link>https://heusser.pro/categories/call-flows/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Call Flows on HEUSSER.PRO</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 08:23:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heusser.pro/categories/call-flows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Simultaneously Forward Calls to Multiple Numbers in Teams</title>
        <link>https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 08:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When configuring call flows in Microsoft Teams, one question I hear a lot is if a call can be forwarded to multiple external numbers at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This most likely applies to after-hours on-call scenarios where it’s absolutely crucial that somebody will eventually answer the call.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/0rL2fJDRh74kKQK7Z.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;1024&#34;
	height=&#34;1024&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/0rL2fJDRh74kKQK7Z_hu2ad6c7f72232edae2cd2c9c9db7e2c67_98921_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/0rL2fJDRh74kKQK7Z_hu2ad6c7f72232edae2cd2c9c9db7e2c67_98921_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, this is impossible with Teams call queues. However, this is by design. The purpose of a queue is that the call stays within the queue and the company has control over the call for the entire flow of the call. In other words, the queue makes sure that the call stays within company boundaries by ignoring all user configured call answering rules. So, if a user has configured his calls to immediately forward to a personal cell phone, the queue simply doesn’t care and will present the call to the user in Teams anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you must forward the call to multiple numbers at the same time, you can use regular Teams (Microsoft 365) users. I always suggest using dedicated, generic accounts for this, even though it’s an additional license cost. This will make management easier and ensures that no user is able to change the forwarding settings and mess with the call flow on their own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I did this in my lab, I used the users I already had to demonstrate this. This means that they have real sounding names and are not generically named accounts like I would use in a real-world scenario.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-to-configure-it&#34;&gt;How To Configure It&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To configure forwarding to multiple external numbers simultaneously, identify where in your auto attendant or call queue the call must be forwarded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, think about to how many numbers the call must be forwarded. Create one Teams enterprise voice enabled user for each external target number. Then create one more Teams voice enabled user. On this user, configure a call group and add all the users which forward to external numbers immediately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set this user’s call forwarding settings to either immediately forward to or also ring the call group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1GFWLa0rX87G1PIvrBqX0jg.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1251&#34;
	height=&#34;640&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1GFWLa0rX87G1PIvrBqX0jg_hub0eccbd257ba91d0aa89c5be8d8b36ad_70703_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1GFWLa0rX87G1PIvrBqX0jg_hub0eccbd257ba91d0aa89c5be8d8b36ad_70703_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;195&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;469px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1Y70lmU10yu9gbNH8JZeJaQ.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1248&#34;
	height=&#34;787&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1Y70lmU10yu9gbNH8JZeJaQ_huf3eb10202199579ef277959d7cb9875b_85825_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1Y70lmU10yu9gbNH8JZeJaQ_huf3eb10202199579ef277959d7cb9875b_85825_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The accounts which are members of the call group must all be configured like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1XH5BluccXOhJiCrPyMkDQ.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1243&#34;
	height=&#34;650&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1XH5BluccXOhJiCrPyMkDQ_hub286ce9cf621796e8b3d36ba6cc30767_74228_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1XH5BluccXOhJiCrPyMkDQ_hub286ce9cf621796e8b3d36ba6cc30767_74228_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;191&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;458px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the first user can be configured to either also ring or immediately forward to the call group, the call group members must be configured to &lt;strong&gt;immediately forward&lt;/strong&gt;. If they’re set to also ring to an external number, it will not work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;call-flowdiagram&#34;&gt;Call Flow Diagram&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I updated the M365 Call Flow Visualizer and added two new parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;-ShowNestedUserCallGroups  
    Specifies if call groups of users should be expanded and included into the diagram.  
    Required:           false  
    Type:               boolean  
    Default value:      false  

-ShowNestedUserDelegates  
    Specifies if delegates s of users should be expanded and included into the diagram.  
    Required:           false  
    Type:               boolean  
    Default value:      false
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This allows us to indefinitely expand and display the user calling settings of call group members and delegates in the diagrams as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that these features are currently only available in the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/mozziemozz/M365CallFlowVisualizer/tree/dev&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;DEV&lt;/a&gt; branch of the GitHub repo. I did my best to thoroughly test this but since there are basically unlimited possibilities of how users are interlinked within user call groups and delegates this is quite hard. There may still be some bugs, if you encounter any, please let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1dgXzEKcsD0wZF74b5qg.png&#34;
	width=&#34;674&#34;
	height=&#34;1694&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1dgXzEKcsD0wZF74b5qg_hu8968c148c4e326bdf2cd2894dfc6106b_90447_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1dgXzEKcsD0wZF74b5qg_hu8968c148c4e326bdf2cd2894dfc6106b_90447_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;39&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;95px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1R6tSs1eHHGO255tRCxAkg.png&#34;
	width=&#34;637&#34;
	height=&#34;1694&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1R6tSs1eHHGO255tRCxAkg_huf0a4e1baf4a8951c61543da928555726_94829_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1R6tSs1eHHGO255tRCxAkg_huf0a4e1baf4a8951c61543da928555726_94829_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;37&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;90px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;other-options&#34;&gt;Other Options&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This also works if you use call delegation instead of a call group with both immediately forward and also ring on the first user. I tested it with Microsoft Calling Plans, but it should work with Direct Routing or Operator Connect as well. The maximum amount of simultaneous external forwards via call group I tested was three and that still worked as expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recommend using a call group over delegates because this gives you a little more flexibility. While delegates will always simultaneously ring all delegates, a call group can be configured for serial ring as well. In this case, it will always ring for &lt;strong&gt;20 seconds&lt;/strong&gt; per call group member before the next one is tried. This time out cannot be changed as of today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;caveats&#34;&gt;Caveats&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you do this, you need to be aware of issues that might occur. At the beginning of this article, I briefly mentioned that the purpose of a queue is to stay in control of the call for the entire time. That’s not the case when using external forwarding on user calling settings. For example, if one of the external targets is not reachable by e.g. having a rather short voicemail timeout, is in flight mode or just has no reception, calls might get lost on personal voicemail boxes outside of a company’s control. Once a call hits any voicemail box, the call is technically connected and will stop ringing the other targets, even if parallel ringing is configured on the call group. This also applies to call groups configured in serial ring. If e.g. the first target is not reachable, and the call goes to voicemail the other targets won’t even be tried anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s also noteworthy that user configured calling settings can become extremely complex and it’s easy for users (or admins for that matter) to build loops or enable forwards without knowing about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The same goes for the M365 Call Flow Visualizer, I don’t think that it’s possible to accurately display everything that’s configured in nested user calling settings. I tried my best to render call flows where a serial ring is configured on a user configured call group though. As an example, I configured the same call group which was already shown in the above diagram for serial ring. Now all the call group targets are displayed in chronological order, and you can see how the call trickles down to the next target after 20 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/14omtG0AeKdTOD4TzNItlA.png&#34;
	width=&#34;690&#34;
	height=&#34;2971&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/14omtG0AeKdTOD4TzNItlA_hu12f6c71221e7d8c038019ced665f10d5_171663_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/14omtG0AeKdTOD4TzNItlA_hu12f6c71221e7d8c038019ced665f10d5_171663_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;23&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;55px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike with call queues and auto attendants, where the M365 Call Flow Visualizer does a fantastic job displaying things as they are, please take complicated nested user call groups and delegate flows with a grain of salt. At least for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look at this call flow for example. When the call gets to &lt;strong&gt;Bill Stearn&lt;/strong&gt; it will also ring his call group in serial order. Thus, it will ring the mobile number &lt;strong&gt;+4178857****&lt;/strong&gt; for 20 seconds. Because there is an unanswered timeout of 20s configured for &lt;strong&gt;Bill&lt;/strong&gt; the call will then be forwarded to his delegates where the call will be forwarded to &lt;strong&gt;Bobby&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Mike&lt;/strong&gt; and they have an immediate forwarding configured to their mobiles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1cZyXiLxV40aMOM5YsXkbUw.png&#34;
	width=&#34;882&#34;
	height=&#34;3730&#34;
	srcset=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1cZyXiLxV40aMOM5YsXkbUw_hu59a321b23c096be65035986b86105a5a_236702_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, https://heusser.pro/p/simultaneously-forward-calls-to-multiple-numbers-in-teams-d228adb805b7/1cZyXiLxV40aMOM5YsXkbUw_hu59a321b23c096be65035986b86105a5a_236702_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;23&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;56px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the users who are members of the call group are linked after each other because the call group is configured in serial ring. The links which point from the delegate sub graph (which is always parallel ring) to the delegate users are still linked to the correct user but it’s not very easy to understand what’s going on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When we think about the delegate flow, the chaining from &lt;strong&gt;Bobby’s&lt;/strong&gt; time out of 20s doesn’t actually apply anymore and the call won’t be forwarded to &lt;strong&gt;Mike&lt;/strong&gt; because that part of the diagram only applies to the serial order of &lt;strong&gt;Bill’s&lt;/strong&gt; call group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, &lt;strong&gt;Wendy&lt;/strong&gt; is also included in the call flow even though a call could never go this far in that specific call flow because of the applied time outs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I currently don’t see any way I could solve this with the visualizer script.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d like to point out that configuring both a call group and delegates on the same user seems extremely unlikely and is something I would generally refrain from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although it’s not an ideal solution, using generic user accounts and call groups for certain scenarios is for sure a creative one. In some cases, this might help you solve a very specific niche scenario which previously seemed impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do recommend using auto attendants and call queues to build your call flows whenever possible. If you must use call groups, I advise you to keep it simple and create generic accounts to which only Teams admins have access to. Otherwise, it’s free-for-all kind of situation and users can mess with your configuration as they please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you stick with simple scenarios (like shown in the first three diagrams in this article) and avoid building call group loops or timeouts which cancel each other out, I don’t see any issues why you shouldn’t do this if you really need to.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Find All Auto Attendants and Call Queues a User is Associated with</title>
        <link>https://heusser.pro/p/find-all-auto-attendants-and-call-queues-a-user-is-associated-with-16710c3adf01/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://heusser.pro/p/find-all-auto-attendants-and-call-queues-a-user-is-associated-with-16710c3adf01/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’d be lying if I said that many people have asked me about such a script. But one person has. Frankly, this was all the motivation I needed. The question was &lt;strong&gt;if there’s a way to see all call flows any user is associated with&lt;/strong&gt;. I figured that I’d take a shot and see if I can come up with anything. And come up I did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, let’s talk about where a Teams User could be configured in a call flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auto Attendant Holiday Call Handlings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auto Attendant Default Call Flows (transfer or IVR option)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auto Attendant After Hours Call Flows (transfer or IVR option)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Auto Attendant Operator (IVR option)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Call Queue Agent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Call Queue Timeout Target (transfer or personal voicemail)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Call Queue Overflow Target (transfer or personal voicemail)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-does-itwork&#34;&gt;How Does it Work?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To achieve this, I’ve modified the M365 Call Flow Visualizer Script. Since the Visualizer is already able to read configurations from Auto Attendants and Call Queues, this wasn’t too hard. All I had to do was to write another function which will pull the Ids of all Voice Apps into an array. I then loop through all the Ids and run the Visualizer for each Voice App. When the Visualizer detects that a call is forwarded to a User at any point in the call flow, the details of said forwarding will be added to a PSObject which will then be added to a variable which only exists in the new function. I called this variable &lt;code&gt;$userLinkVoiceApps&lt;/code&gt; . Because the Visualizer is running for each Voice App, this variable must exist outside of the main script. Otherwise, it would get overwritten after each run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;. .\Functions\Find-CallQueueAndAutoAttendantUserLinks.ps1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;. Find-CallQueueAndAutoAttendantUserLinks -SearchScope All&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve added this script to my &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/mozziemozz/M365CallFlowVisualizer/blob/main/CallFlowUserFinder.ps1&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;repository&lt;/a&gt;. Make sure you clone the whole repo or download it as a zip file so that all relative file paths work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don’t specify the &lt;code&gt;-SearchUserId&lt;/code&gt; you will be able to select a user from the Out-GridView Table. Otherwise, you can pass an Azure AD ObjectId to the function using this parameter. You can also limit the search scope to just &lt;code&gt;AutoAttendants&lt;/code&gt;or &lt;code&gt;CallQueues&lt;/code&gt; . By default, the search Scope &lt;code&gt;All&lt;/code&gt; is used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The M365CallFlowVisualizer.ps1 is run with the parameters shown below. The &lt;code&gt;-FindUserLinks&lt;/code&gt; switch tells the script to write all user related information into the external &lt;code&gt;$userLinkVoiceApps&lt;/code&gt; variable. Since we’re running the script for each Voice App anyway, there’s no point in expanding nested call flows. We don’t need to create diagrams either, therefore all diagram output options are disabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;. .\M365CallFlowVisualizerV2.ps1 -Identity $searchScopeIncludedVoiceApp -FindUserLinks -SaveToFile $false -SetClipBoard $false -ExportHtml $false -ShowNestedCallFlows $false -ShowUserCallingSettings $false&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on the amount of Voice Apps you have, it will take some time to finish. After all the information has been gathered, it will be exported to a CSV file at&lt;code&gt;.\Output\VoiceAppsLinkedTo_$UserId.csv&lt;/code&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s an example of the generated output (the actual output will also include User Ids and Voice App Ids). We’re now able to see to which Voice Apps and where in these Voice Apps a user is configured at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;good-toknow&#34;&gt;Good to Know&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The M365 Call Flow Visualizer does not support reading IVRs on Holiday Call Handlings. Thus, this script won’t be able to tell if a user is linked to an Auto Attendant on a Holiday IVR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Visualizer is built in a way in which it represents an accurate diagram of the &lt;strong&gt;active&lt;/strong&gt; configuration of a Voice App. For example, if you’ve configured an Operator but it isn’t linked to an IVR menu option, the Operator won’t be drawn in the diagram, even if it’s present in the configuration. The same goes for configured after hours call flows, which don’t use a schedule (in which case the default call flow is active all the time). Because of that, the script won’t include users which are configured on &lt;strong&gt;inactive&lt;/strong&gt; configurations on Auto Attendants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Call Queues which are configured to either immediately time out or overflow it’s a little bit different. The Visualizer won’t draw the call distribution subgraph because there’s no distribution happening when zero-time outs or overflows are configured but the agent will still be included in the exported CSV file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here we can see that the Call Queue “PS Test CQ” immediately overflows to an external number.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Teams Admin Center, agents are assigned using a Team though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you would like to learn more about Call Queues and Agent Lists, please refer to &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://heusser.pro/p/microsoft-teams-call-queue-agent-lists-and-how-to-force-sync-them-ef8092090df0&#34; &gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, the CallFlowUserFinder.ps1 will still include this user in the exported table so that you can see all the Queues a user is associated with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that this script/method helps you figure which Voice Apps a specific user is linked to.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
